IUE-CWA Local 301; Records apap023
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Grievance Files, 1959-1999; 8
  - Grievance Files, 1967-1969; 1971; 1972; 1974; 1977-1979 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 2)
  - Grievance Files, 1967-1972; 1974-1981 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 3)
  - Grievance Files, 1990 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4)
  - Grievance Files, 1990; 1991; 1992 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5)
  - Grievance Files, 1991 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Grievance Files, 1991; 1992 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 8)
  - Grievance Files, 1992; 1993 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 9)
  - Grievance Files, 1993; 1994 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10)
  - Grievance Files, 1987; 1994-1995 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11)
  - Grievance Files, 1987 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Grievance Files, 1987; 1988 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 28 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16-21)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 29 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-5)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1981 (Box 29 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 29 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 7-17)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1980 (Box 29 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 18)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 29 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 30 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-4)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 30 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 30 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 6-17)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 30 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 18)
  - Grievance Files, 1975 (Box 30 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 19-24)
  - Grievance Files, 1975 (Box 31 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-11)
  - Grievance Files, 1987-1990; 1993 (Box 31 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 12)
  - Grievance Files, 1994-1996 (Box 31 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 31 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14-17)
  - Grievance Files, 1981 (Box 31 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 18)
  - Grievance Files, 1980; 1981 (Box 31 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 19)
  - Grievance Files, 1980 (Box 31 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 20-21)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1980 (Box 31 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 22)
  - Grievance Files, 1977 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-3)
  - Grievance Files, 1977; 1978 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 4)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 5-7)
  - Grievance Files, 1984 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Grievance Files, 1984; 1985 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10)
  - Grievance Files, 1984 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Grievance Files, 1984; 1985 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1983; 1984 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1982; 1983; 1984; 1985 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15)
  - Grievance Files, 1984; 1985 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16)
  - Grievance Files, 1983; 1984 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 17)
  - Grievance Files, 1988; 1989 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 18-19)
  - Grievance Files, 1990 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 20)
  - Grievance Files, 1984; 1985 (Box 32 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 21)
  - Grievance Files, 1978 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-13)
  - Grievance Files, 1967; 1980-1984; 1991; 1996 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1982-1984 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15)
  - Grievance Files, 1991; 1992 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16)
  - Grievance Files, 1992 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 17)
  - Grievance Files, 1993 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 18)
  - Grievance Files, 1994-1996 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 19)
  - Grievance Files, 1984 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 20)
  - Grievance Files, 1985 (Box 33 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 21-22)
  - Grievance Files, 1979 (Box 34 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 1-9)
  - Grievance Files, 1999 (Box 34 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 10-12)
  - Grievance Files, 1975-1976; 1978; 1992-1994 (Box 34 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 13)
  - Grievance Files, 1987-1996 (Box 34 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 14)
  - Grievance Files, 1970; 1971; 1973; 1975-1977; 1982-1985 (Box 34 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 15)
  - Grievance Files, 1984-1985 (Box 34 (8-Grievance Files), Folder 16)
- Arbitration Files, 1960-1997; 9
  Series 9 contains grievances that made their way to arbitration from 1960-1997. These files contain documents relating to the actions taken on grievances that led to arbitration as well as transcripts from the arbitration hearings.
  - Case 5230010767, 1966 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1)
  - Case 1530055482, 1982 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 2)
  - Case 1530069282, 1982 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 3)
  - Case 1530005184, 1984 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 4)
  - Case 1530018383, 1983 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Case 1530062283, 1983 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 7)
  - Case 1530005284, 1984 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Case 1530016268, 1968 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 10-11)
  - Case 1530013568, 1968 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Case 1530009870, 1970 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Case 1530010070, 1970 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Case 1530014770, 1970 (Box 1 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 18-19)
  - Case 1530000883, 1983 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1)
  - Case 11E3000075597, 1997 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1)
  - Case 153000046990, 1991 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 2)
  - Case 1530065683, 1983 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 2)
  - Case 1S30065683, 1984 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 3)
  - Case L3817SYRL3263, 1963 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 4)
  - Case L44643SYRL13364, 1965 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 5)
  - Case 1530003566, 1966 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 6)
  - Case 1530014466, 1967 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 7)
  - Case 1530004567, 1963 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 8)
  - Case 1530002568, 1968 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 9)
  - Case 1530002568, 1968 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 9)
  - Case 1530017668, 1969 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 10)
  - Case 1530009968, 1968 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 11)
  - Case 1530015068, 1969 (Box 2 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 12)
  - Case 15 30 0173 70, 1970 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1-2)
  - Case 11 300 00890 93, 1993 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 3)
  - Case 15 30 0196 71, 1971 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 4-5)
  - Case 15 30 0123 71, 1971 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Case 15 30 0060 71, 1971 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 8)
  - Case 15 30 0093 71, 1971 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 9-10)
  - Case 638-8276178, 1982-1984 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 11)
  - Discharge Case, 1963; 1965-1966 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 12)
  - Case 365-7025370, 1970; 1974 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 13)
  - Case 1773-7545808, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 14)
  - Case 7877-7753807, 1977; 1980 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 15)
  - Case 3879-7648425, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Material, 1954-1980 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 17)
  - Case 8185-7754690, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 18)
  - Case No. 1530-0188-74. N.D. 37715, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1)
  - Case No. 15-30-0224-75. N.D. 41407, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 2)
  - Case No. 15-30-0254-75. N.D. 43, 648, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 3)
  - Case No. 15-30-0172-75. N.D. 42936, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 4)
  - Case No. 15-30-0179-75. N.D. 43, 177, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 5)
  - Case No. 15-30-0118-75. N.D. 41, 839, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 6)
  - Case No. 15-30-0227-75. N.D. 43, 168, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 7)
  - Case No. 15-30-0201-76. N.D. 47159, 1976 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 8)
  - Case No. 15-30-0293-76. N.D. 47820, 1976 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 9)
  - Case No. 15-30-0293-76. In the Matter of the Arbitration of IUE Radio and Machine Workers, 1976 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 10)
  - Case No. 15-30-0473-76. N.D. 48848, 1977 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 11)
  - Case No. 15-30-0590-76. N.D. 49148, 1976 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 12)
  - Case No. 15-30-0126-76. N.D. 47031, 1976 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 13)
  - Case No. 15-30-0096-76. N.D. 46723, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 14)
  - Case No. 15-30-0615-76. N.D. 45535, 1977 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 15)
  - Arbitration Hearings, 1977 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 16)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1976 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 17)
  - Arbitration Awards, 1975 (Box 4 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Status Sheet, 1983-1985 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1)
  - Arbitrations, Case #5681-8065332, 1980; 1981 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 2)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8358-8170221, 1981 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 3)
  - Arbitrations, Case #5161-7334950, 1973; 1974 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 4)
  - Arbitrations, Case #4820-8063991, 1977; 1980 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 5)
  - Arbitrations, Case #6924-8067178, 1979; 1980; 1981 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Arbitrations, Case #1352-8276874, 1982; 1983 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 8)
  - Arbitrations, Case #1304-8276874, 1982; 1983 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 9)
  - Arbitrations, Case #7849-8169076, 1980; 1981; 1983 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 10)
  - Arbitrations, Case #7892-8169202, 1981 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 11)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8758-8170918, 1981; 1982 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 12)
  - Arbitrations, Case #7773-8169144, 1982 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 13)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8739-8170851, 1981 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 14)
  - Arbitrations, Case #15-30-1110-84, 1985 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 15)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8864-91, 1991; 1993 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 16)
  - Arbitrations, Case #5662-8586233, 1982; 1985; 1986 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 17-18)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8726-90, ca. 1980-1992 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 19)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8864-91105174, 1991 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 20)
  - Arbitrations, Case #148-95113901, 1995; 1996 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 21)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8700-90103705, 1990 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 22)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8702-90103707, 1990; 1991 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 23)
  - Arbitrations, with Grievances 103705, 103706, 103707, 1990; 1991 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 24)
  - Arbitrations, Case #8407-89100719, 1989 (Box 5 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 25)
  - Arbitrations, Case #398-96115256, 1996; 1997 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1)
  - Arbitrations, 1994; 1995; 1997 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 2)
  - Arbitrations, Case #3819-8381242, 1984; 1985 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 3)
  - Arbitrations, Case #4414-8482347, 1984; 1985; 1986 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 4)
  - Arbitrations, Case #3720-831110, 1984; 1985 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 5)
  - Arbitrations, Case #5539-8586193, 1985 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 6)
  - Arbitrations, Case #5829-8588261, 1985; 1986 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 7)
  - Arbitrations, Case #5811-8586583, 1985 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 8)
  - Arbitrations, Case #4654-8487723, 1985; 1986; 1987 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 9)
  - Arbitrations, Case #5125-8484949, 1985; 1986 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 10)
  - Arbitrations, Between General Electric Company & I.U.E 119 #42155, 1976 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 11)
  - Arbitrations, NY Agenda Copies, General Electric Company, 1990 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 12)
  - Arbitrations, 1982 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 13)
  - Arbitrations, Between General Electric Company & Local 161, 1970-1973 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 14)
  - Arbitrations, Newspaper Clippings, 1986 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 15)
  - Arbitrations, General Electric Company & Local 301, National Labor Relations Board, 1993; 1994 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 16)
  - Arbitrations, Notice to Take Deposition, 1966 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 17)
  - Arbitrations, Order to Show Cause, 1969 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 18)
  - Arbitrations, Notice of Appeal, 1969; 1984 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 19)
  - Arbitrations, National Labor Relations Board vs. Local 301, 1969; 1970 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 20)
  - Arbitrations, National Labor Relations Board, Related Information, 1969; 1970 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 21)
  - Arbitrations, "Red Circle", Job Evaluations, 1965-1969; 1992 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 22)
  - Arbitrations, Job Placement, Inspection, Benefits, 1980; 1984-1985; 1986; 1990; 1993 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 23)
  - Arbitrations, Scheduled Vacation Shutdowns, 1974-1977; 1981-1986; 1988; 1991-1992 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 24)
  - Arbitrations, Agreement of Indemnification, 1959 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 25)
  - Arbitrations, Job Combinations, 1987 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 26)
  - Arbitrations, The Changing NLRB Law, Miscellaneous Rulings, 1984-1985 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 27)
  - Arbitrations, B. Davis vs. General Electric Company, 1986 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 28)
  - Arbitrations, Deposition and Affidavits, Conto vs. General Electric Company, 1985-1986 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 29)
  - Arbitrations, Order to Show Cause and Summons, L. Valenti vs. General Electric Company, 1983 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 30)
  - Arbitrations, Notice Vacating Stipulation and Re-instating Action, 1976 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 31)
  - Arbitrations, Third Part Summons Plaintiff L. Breckenridge, 1982 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 32)
  - Arbitrations, Miscellaneous, 1977; 1979; 1980; 1985 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 33)
  - Arbitrations, Awards, 1977-1979 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 34)
  - Arbitrations, National Labor Relations Board, 1986; 1992 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 35)
  - Arbitrations, Human Relations, 1977-1978 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 36)
  - Arbitrations, Case# 569-8275398, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 37)
  - Arbitrations, Case# 939-8275804, 1983 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 38)
  - Arbitrations, Case#1160-8276572, 1983 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 39)
  - Arbitrations, Case#1255-7026491, 1970-1971 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 40)
  - Arbitrations, Case#1018-7025917, 1970-1971 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 41)
  - Arbitrations, Case#600-7025369, 1970-1971 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 42)
  - Arbitrations, Case#432-7024920, 1970-1971 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 43)
  - Arbitrations, Case#1557-7545756, 1975-1976 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 44)
  - Arbitrations, Case#1320-7545427, 1975-1976 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 45)
  - Arbitrations, Case#5843-7750973, 1977 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 46)
  - Arbitrations and Grievance, Case#5880-7751180, 1978 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 47)
  - Arbitrations, Case#5614-7651183, 1976-1977 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 48-49)
  - Arbitrations, Case#767-8275686, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 49)
  - Arbitrations, 1974 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1)
  - Arbitrations, 1973 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 2)
  - Arbitrations, 1972 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 3)
  - Arbitrations, 1971 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 4)
  - Arbitrations, 1970 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 5-6)
  - Arbitrations, 1969 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 7-8)
  - Arbitrations, 1968 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 9-10)
  - Arbitrations, 1967 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 11)
  - Arbitrations, 1965; 1966 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Arbitrations, 1961; 1962 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 14-15)
  - Arbitrations, 1960 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 16)
  - Arbitrations, 1960; 1963 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 17)
  - Arbitrations, 1963; 1964 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 18)
  - Arbitrations, 1963 (Box 7 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 19)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-7011-3, 1996 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 1)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-7011-1, 3-CB-7011-2, Undated (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 2)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case E-740-82, 1983 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 3)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case E-776-83, 1984 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 4)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Charged Against GE for Unfair Labor Practice, 1994 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 5)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case No. 3-CA-12631, 3-CB-4648, 1985 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 6)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4898, 1986 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 7)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4768, 1985 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 8)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4808, 1985 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 9)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4650, 1985 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 10)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4648, 1985 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 11)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4517, 1984 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 12)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4236, 1983 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 13)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CA-11457, 1983 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 14)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CA-11693, 1983 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 15)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4338, 1983 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 16)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4299, 1983 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 17)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4254, 1983 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 18)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-4033, 1982 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 19)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CA-10264, 1981 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 20)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-3946, 1981 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 21)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-3730, 1980 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 22)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-3481, 1979 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 23)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-3415, 1979 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 24)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-3352, 1979 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 25)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-3149, 1978 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 26)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-2532, 1975 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 27)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-2188, 1973 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 28)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-2141, 1973 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 29)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-1836, 1972 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 30)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 2-CA-11911, 1971 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 31)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-1456, 1970 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 32)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CA-4072, 1970 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 33)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-1464, 1970 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 34)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CC-515, 1969 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 35)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CC_513, 1969 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 36)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-7011-1, 1996 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 37)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-7011-2, 1996 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 38)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 3-CB-7011-3, 1996 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 39)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 4-E-N-875-107859E, 1985 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 40)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case 4-E-D-83-92439, 1983 (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 41)
  - National Labor Relations Board, Case IV-E-N-2119-77E, E-N-50766-77E (Box 8 (9-Arbitration Files), Folder 42)